rent-acoder.com 2018-08-31

# Privacy policy - Qualified web programmers and designers

Rent A Coder (We, Us, dot com systems) is committed to respecting your right to privacy while using our site.

This Privacy policy contains information regarding our privacy practices for the entire site and subsidiary sites.

**Information Collection and Use  **

Rent-ACoder.com is the sole owner of the customer information collected on this site. We will not share this information in any ways other than those disclosed in this statement. [Rent-ACoder.com](http://www.rent-acoder.com/) collects information from his users at several points on the website.

**Information Requests  **

Throughout our site, you are provided with the opportunity to contact us via email to ask questions, request information and materials, register for online presentations, or provide comments and suggestions. You may also be offered the opportunity to have one of our representatives contact you to provide information about our products or services. We may request additional personal information from you, such as your name, telephone number, address, copy of a valid identification card to help us satisfy your request.

**Suppliers  **

We outsource credit card processing. The companies that perform these services do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

**Links  **

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that [Rent-ACoder.com](http://www.rent-acoder.com/) is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the [Rent-ACoder.com](http://www.rent-acoder.com/) website.

**Questions  **

If you have questions, or if you feel we are in violation of this privacy policy, please email [payments [at] Rent-ACoder.com](mailto:payments@rent-acoder.com)

**Sessions and cookies**

Our Site uses cookies / sessions to give you a better experience on the website and to generate statistics.

**Personal Information  **

Any information we collect, including your e-mail and mailing address, are not shared with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes except newsletters from the Rent-Acoder.com site.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. No one can view your account information without your password, which you can change anytime you want. Credit Card information is not an issue since [Rent-ACoder.com](http://www.rent-acoder.com/) uses a third party service for secure credit card transactions.

The use of our Web Site is solely at their own risk on an "as is", "as available" basis. Information on our website is provided for general purposes only and is not intended to render accounting, tax, consultative, investment, consulting, legal or other professional advice or services, in any form.

This website uses cookies to offer you the best experience online and for statistical purposes. By continuing to use our website, you agree to the use of cookies.Close message
